Description:
  List all registered routes

Usage:
  route:list [options]

Options:
      --json                       Output the route list as JSON
      --method[=METHOD]            Filter the routes by method
      --action[=ACTION]            Filter the routes by action
      --name[=NAME]                Filter the routes by name
      --domain[=DOMAIN]            Filter the routes by domain
      --middleware[=MIDDLEWARE]    Filter the routes by middleware
      --path[=PATH]                Only show routes matching the given path pattern
      --except-path[=EXCEPT-PATH]  Do not display the routes matching the given path pattern
  -r, --reverse                    Reverse the ordering of the routes
      --sort[=SORT]                The column (domain, method, uri, name, action, middleware, definition) to sort by [default: "uri"]
      --except-vendor              Do not display routes defined by vendor packages
      --only-vendor                Only display routes defined by vendor packages
  -h, --help                       Display help for the given command. When no command is given display help for the list command
      --silent                     Do not output any message
  -q, --quiet                      Only errors are displayed. All other output is suppressed
  -V, --version                    Display this application version
      --ansi|--no-ansi             Force (or disable --no-ansi) ANSI output
  -n, --no-interaction             Do not ask any interactive question
      --env[=ENV]                  The environment the command should run under
  -v|vv|vvv, --verbose             Increase the verbosity of messages: 1 for normal output, 2 for more verbose output and 3 for debug
